do you use the potato stack yourself or not yeah i did edit because i started with grogbot
and i decided to have it give me notifications on incoming tickets check the ticket and then give
me a concept of an email that can be replied and i either choose yes no or i get feedback on the
concept so it can improve the email and then reply because the usage goes so fast i don't want to use
it for coding yeah i don't want to run out in in four hours and then have to wait a full week
yeah but it got a bit out of hand first i had one pot and i told it well i also have people who were
supposed to send the email to the ticket system emailing me direct so scrape my mailbox forward
tickets i have a slack a notification on incoming tickets and other bots gives the concept and then
i tried to add another bot i said hey if it is a wordpress question about updating content on the
wordpress i have a system with one click login where you get a normal writer account no admin
account you can update the text please try it and before i knew i had a full flow of tickets coming
in where people were asking me to change text on their website and the bot did it it gave me the
solution to add another bot for quality checks it checked it they communicated and then it told me
check this link here it's online i check it i approve and email goes back and it even wrote
down hours where we can build a customer so that's like a full employee and then my usage was going
like skyrocketing within a few hours and that's where i used the eggbot from lawren from potato
and it's a yeah you have like 8k tokens for each and a prompt that you're using and it is scaled
down to 500 instead of 8k and i've been testing now for three days and it is really tight it works
perfectly i have no issues so she's saving me a lot of tokens if you tell i'd now put it on a
repeat i gave the the eggbot repetitive task to monday night check all my bots check the entire
flow check all the routines and optimize everything and the eggbot is even taking routines from certain
bots away and saying hey this needs to be a separate bot because if it has only one task it
focuses on that task and it has less tokens than when you are doing three tasks at the same time
yeah so do you still have like the chief of staff and you talk to only him and then he dispatch
stuff yeah yeah yeah i just have one point of communication no we we have waybooks right it
should not even be a chron drops it should be an event yeah crypto daily should be my crypto
channel but maybe i'm gonna nuke this one because i can save some token do you have the eggbot in
it yes here yeah just tell it to to check everything and optimize it and give you a
proposal on what will be better and ask it how many tokens you can save i can't because
i don't have usage oh yay of course i have some issue with i don't know if you have that see like
i have a message etc etc and i i need to ask the status about the task sometimes it doesn't give me
the response to it it's kind of yeah sometimes it's like it's skipping some things yeah checking
all of the status about all tasks running both formulas report blah blah blah so he's asking
the whole team like what to do if i have like 20 both then i'm burning token like crazy right
yeah mastering that you can you could even like have one job pair grok but super grok account stuff
yeah but it works like the same normal dev team if you just have everybody talking to everybody
at the end of the day they only work two hours and if you fully optimize it and are really strict on
your communication and optimize everything then you have a perfect dev team who works like seven
and a half of the eight hours so that's what you want to do here as well personally i should change
it to not code and just open prs and then i have the other agents codex cloud grok yeah build stuff
from those prs yeah they work on ship yet codes and that's exactly so only management verification
is all you need yes the most critical skills to have in your toolbox is a high quality
verification skill yeah like something like something for cicd right like you want to
disrupt the disloped skills of the p stack is really good i haven't tried it you should yeah
but okay i don't know if you should because you have also like legacy project stuff that you
should not refactor too much oh no no that will break everything i don't know if a disloped stuff
will refactor the whole code base for you and you will have a 24-hour session and you don't know why
because you disloped it let's be the verification skill together a create verification skill yeah
that's why in my grok bot it mentioned create verification skill because yeah i dropped the
articles so create verification skill dr heck bot that's what we both installed i think we need the
own v stack stack bro yeah but yeah there are so many options right now but on the other hand
i am waiting for this to be integrated into cursor i mean that that's it like you can create your
skill and then it's they're not going to standardize p stack to all of the things i mean
maybe they do it like in the back end you know yeah yeah but that's that's what i mean so they
integrate something like this because if so many people are using it and their internal teams are
doing it as well then why not make it a part of yeah cursor and just have it for everybody
available without adding additional integrations and plugins yeah yeah i mean but for them it's
make even more sense to keep as plug-inable friendly stuff then everyone is turning them
into their own use case right like everyone building their name stack because an ios developer
will not have the same needs than no that's a react to right so yes and also i like a lot of
developers wants to have control of their own stack and slash way of coding and stuff like that
right no junk in it so she has a skill to maintain it yeah that makes sense i have a skill to clean
up work trees and branches after i deploy right so why not i have p stack the tag bot yes and the
bot is using p stack into our own setup right my bot that helps to create high quality bot your
roster ships with space tag yes okay okay so what did we learn or what did we expect from grogbot to
come next grogbot is awesome but you have to optimize it otherwise you go out of tokens in
the day and you can't use it so we use her solution for adding eggbot and we just say
optimize everything and it's fixed yeah yeah you ask to optimize and then it's done and it did
yeah i need to do it okay i need to wait a couple of hours but after that should be fine
yes thank you everyone thank you for commenting and thank you arinad for joining us during the
live subscribe left the video like the video share it and i will see you next time next week next
time same place bye-bye